https://rad-ra.com/privacy-policy/

This is the Website of RAD
Our postal address is:
319 S. First Street
Tipp City, OH 45371
Email Address: info@rad-ra.com
RAD Sites are committed to respecting your privacy and recognizing your need for appropriate protection and management of personally identifiable information you share with us (the phrases “personally identifiable information” or “personal information” mean any information by which you can be identified, such as your name, address, telephone number, etc.). This privacy policy is intended to inform you of what personally identifiable information or personal information we may collect from you when you visit our Websites.
Your access to and continued use of the RAD website (the “Site”) constitutes your acceptance of, and is conditional upon your continued acceptance of and compliance with, the following provisions (the “Terms of Use”).
USE OF THE RAD SITE
You can browse the contents of RAD’s website without telling us who you are and without revealing any personal information. You may download or copy the Contents and other downloadable materials displayed on the Site for your personal use only. You acknowledge, however, that this site contains information, data, photographs, graphics and other materials that are protected by laws governing copyrights, trademarks, trade secrets, and other proprietary rights. Under no circumstances may you transfer (including, without limitation, by sale, loan, rent or lease), use, copy, reproduce, download, republish, upload, post, transmit, adapt, modify or distribute the site contents, in whole or in part, without the express prior written consent of RAD. The use of any of the site contents on any other website or networked computer environment is prohibited.
You expressly agree that the use of this site is at your own risk. Neither RAD nor its officers, directors, employees, agents, affiliates nor any person involved in creating, producing or distributing the site warrant that the site will be uninterrupted or error free, nor do they make any warranty as to the results that may be obtained from the use of the site or to the accuracy or currency of the information.
The site contents are provided “as is” and without warranties of any kind either express or implied to the fullest extent permissible pursuant to applicable law. RAD assumes no obligation to update the content on the Site or advise on further developments concerning subject matter mentioned. RAD has made every effort to display as accurately as possible a description of its products and services.
Further, RAD does not warrant or make any representation concerning the accuracy or reliability of the materials on this Site or on any websites linked to this Site.
In no event shall RAD or its subsidiaries, affiliates, contractors, agents, directors, officers, employees, or licensors be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, direct, indirect, consequential, incidental, special, punitive, exemplary or general damages, damages for loss of profit or data, or due to business interruption) howsoever caused, including those arising from negligence, or arising out of the use of, or inability to use, the materials on the Site, even if RAD, or a RAD authorized representative, has been notified orally, or in writing, of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability, for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.
COPYRIGHTS and TRADEMARKS
Unless otherwise noted, all materials, including images, text, illustrations, designs, icons, photographs, programs, written and other materials that are part of this Site (collectively, the “Contents”) are copyrights, trademarks, trade dress and/or other intellectual property owned, controlled or licensed by RAD, one of its affiliates or by third parties who have licensed their materials to RAD. The compilation (meaning the collection, arrangement, and assembly) of all content on this Site is the exclusive property of RAD.
RAD and its suppliers and licensors expressly reserve all intellectual property rights in all text, programs, products, processes, technology, content and other materials which appear on this Site. Access to this Site does not confer and shall not be considered as conferring upon anyone any license under any of RAD’s or any third party’s intellectual property rights.
RAD names and logos and all related product and service names, design marks and slogans are the trademarks or service marks of RAD. All other marks are the property of their respective companies. No trademark or service mark license is granted in connection with the materials contained on this Site. Access to this Site does not authorize anyone to use any name, logo or mark in any manner.
COOKIES
RAD Sites use “cookies.” A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Generally, we use cookies to remind us of who you are, estimate our audience size, assist in tracking visits, and/or analyze your visiting patterns. You can generally set your browser to not accept cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it.
However, by not accepting cookies, this may impede your ability to use our site.
We may contract with third parties who may use cookies and collect information on our behalf. These third parties are prohibited by our contract with them from sharing that information with anyone other than us or our Service Providers.
LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES
Our Sites may contain links to Websites operated and maintained by third parties, over which we have no control. Privacy policies on such linked sites may be different from the RAD site privacy policy. You access such linked sites at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a linked site before disclosing any personal information on those sites.
POLICY CHANGES
From time to time, it may become necessary for us to change our privacy policy in whole or in part. If we do so, the new policy will be posted on our Website. Those changes will go into effect on the date posted in the notice. The new policy will apply to all current and past users of our Website and will replace any prior policies that may be inconsistent. This policy was posted in May 2009.
Click Here
937-667-5705937-667-7602info@rad-ra.comEmployment Opportunities | Privacy Policy | Site Map
ISO-9001:2015
©2019 All Rights Reserved by RAD.
Menu
(+1) 937-667-5705
Menu
HomeAbout RADProductsProductsCollision SensorsCollision SensorsPneumaticPneumatic High-AnglePneumatic Spring AssistPneumatic Stainless SteelSpring-LoadedCompliance DevicesCompliance DevicesPneumaticSpring-LoadedDeburring ToolsDeburring ToolsAir MotorParallel GrippersParallel Grippers2-Jaw3-JawColletTool ChangersTool ChangersAutomaticProduct DownloadsProduct DownloadsCollision SensorsCompliance DevicesDeburring ToolsGrippersTool ChangersLegacy ProductsProduct VideoProduct SupportProduct SupportPlacing an OrderConsignment ProgramProduct WarrantyPayment TermsDeliveryReturn PolicyServiceSpare PartsLegacy ProductsGet A QuoteRAD BlogGet A Quote
